Now everybody lift your hands up!
Sing about what you are dreaming!
Always stand up!
Raise up the flag that can't be beaten!
Gotta keep up!
We'll get past every wall that's
in our wake, go without hesitation!
Hands up!
We just have to press on a little more.
To get to the answers we're looking for.
We came to this new world believing That
surely someday we just might find the way.
All the pieces of our dreams
have now come together.
Our bonds won't waver.
With our dreaming hand.
Let's head on towards.
A bright new future.
Now everybody lift your hands up.
Sing about what you are dreaming.
Always stand up.
Raise up the flag that you believe in.
Gotta keep up.
We'll get past everyone that's in our way.
Let's head on never stopping.
Only look up.
Keep your head up way up high.
Always step up.
If waves are rough, jump to the sky.
Never give up.
Our wishes, they will come together.
And lead us on for the future.
We drift on riding the waves.
Towards another shore day by day.
There are many meetings, many goodbyes.
Underneath the flag we fly.
I'll remember the pain within.
I'll keep it in my heart forever.
And never take it lightly.
But I won't surrender.
This freedom I will keep in mind.
I'll keep holding on, never stop it.
Now everybody lift your hands up.
Sing about what you are dreaming.
Always stand up.
Raise up the flag that you believe in.
Gotta keep up.
We'll get past everyone that's in our way.
Let's head on, never stop it.
Only look up.
Keep your head up way up high.
Always step up.
If brains are rough, jump to the sky.
Never give up.
Our wishes, they will come together.
And lead us on for the future.
Hands up.
It's called guard point.
It's one of six different
forms you can change into.
It'll just change on a whim?
You'll do it.
Hey, I'm not a toy, so
quit playing with me.
Seriously?
The samurai just ditched us? Yes. Damn it!
I thought it was a little
too quiet around here.
When I mentioned that I had
fought with a lone torso earlier,
he asked me where I had seen it.
I told him I lost it
somewhere around the lake.
That's when he went storming off, presumably
to go and look for his missing middle.
I must have missed it because I
was distracted by Nami's sexy body.
What does it matter to you, Sanji?
I'm the one who took him out of
the cell and brought him with us.
The poor guy he couldn't move,
like it or not—I'm
responsible for the guy.
If
anything were to happen
to him, it'd be my fault.
I see he can't hold a sword, therefore,
if an enemy were to attack him,
all that he could do is run away.
Well, what now?
He could be in danger, damn it!
Let's go find him. Luffy!
I'll be right back.
You just stay put.
I'll make you a deal.
I'll show you the way only
if you show me your pennies.
Works for me!
Oh man, I'm still.
still I'm still wishing I had a camera.
Oh, no, you don't!
Hey, you've got to go with them.
If Zoro's there, that means Sanji will
be too busy arguing with them to be lewd.
I can't believe I'm
being forced to go search
for that farting samurai in this weather.
just because you can't control yourself!
You idiot!
Do you think I want you here?
I want to be around guys who can share
in my happiness, not a loser like you!
Why was I the only one hit?
I hope I didn't break a bone.
All right, we need to come up with a plan?
Where do we go from here?
First things first.
We need to get our regular
bodies back as soon as possible.
I'm sick and tired of being a giant perv.
Oh, come on You know you love me, Nami.
Franky, don't smile with his face!
It's creepy—you're no fun.
So, about the ankle biters, what do we do?
Any bright ideas?
Franky, I beg you, please don't
speak while you're in choppers' body!
Not one word!
You find something,
mister?
Well, we'll see soon enough.
enough
What?
This can't be right.
You're acting weird, Tim!
Are you feeling so...
What happened?
I don't know, the big guy
just started flipping out!
I can't breathe!
Hey, Chunker!
He says he's having a hard time breathing!
Think you can help him?
Mocha!
Children, what's the matter?
Dolan, too?
All of a sudden, the big
kids are dropping like flies.
Any idea why?
Topper, you find anything?
Please tell us.
I guess the kids really were sick, huh?
You're wrong.
Saint, is there something
that you want right now?
What do you usually do this time of day?
This time of day?
Well, I have a checkup after that.
Go on, what happens next?
I get some candy.
Candy?
It's the best ever.
Everyone loves it
because it's super yummy.
It is, and it's a lot of fun too. What?
Yeah, because smoke comes out of it.
It's really cool, you know.
Maybe that's what I need.
When I eat it, I feel happy.
So, if I have some candy,
then I might feel better.
What was your name? Brownbeard?
Do you know anything about this?
These children, they're
not sick after all.
What are you saying?
I'm never in the lab.
I don't know what goes on
here, but I do know this.
These youngsters are suffering
from an incurable disease.
It's all right. Stay with us.
Hey, Chomper, the smaller ones
are starting to break down too.
The master is merciful.
He went out of his way to bring them here.
And he did it because he hoped
to find a cure for their disease.
He's a scientist of love.
I can't breathe. Allie?
Just look at what you've done to them.
They're suffering because
they left the laboratory.
If they've been able to get their daily
treatment, they would be fine right now.
No way. What's wrong?
What did you find out, NHC 10?
I detected it in their sweat samples.
It's only a trace amount,
but still this is a stimulant.
They've been drugged
afraid, so they aren't sick.
They're going through
NHC 10 withdrawals only.
A select group of doctors from chosen
countries are allowed to use it.
I know. because Dr.
Kureha was one of them.
While it's helpful in curing diseases,
it's used sparingly because
it's highly addictive.
From what I can tell from my research,
the kids have been consuming small
amounts of it each and every day,
and they've slowly become dependent on it.
If they'd go without it,
they'd crave another dose to ease
the pain of their withdrawals.
Who would do this?
And to... children!
Your master's responsible
for this, isn't he?
If he's a savior, then why'd he drug them?
Was it so they can't escape?
What the hell does he want with them?
Watch your mouth.
Insult the master and I'll make you pay.
Chopper, what now?
The kids keep collapsing.
Candy.
You want candy?
Okay, do you want me to go
get some from the lab for you?
No!
As much as they want it, we
can't let him have it anymore.
That's where it came from.
They were unaware that they
were ingesting the drug because
it was hidden in the candy
You've gotta help me Straw Hat.
I really need a piece of candy
Are you gonna get it for me?
Sorry, but I can't choppers the doctor
of my crew I trust him. Whatever.
He says goes so I can't do it.
No fair
Why?
Why?!
His eyes!
What's wrong with him?!
It's scary!
Meany!
You said you'd get it for me!
Just do it already!
You said you were gonna get it!
Go get my candy!
Where is the boy's strength coming from?
Stop, Saint! Calm down!
Something's way wrong!
I've never seen him like this before!
Damn, that kid is strong!
Well, of course he is!
What did you expect from a giant?
But he's just a kid!
Why can't I have my kid?
No!
He's not a giant, mister!
All of us used to be normal size.
At least, until we came to this island.
I thought maybe our disease
made us grow too much.
Because that's the only
thing wrong with us.
There are plenty of strange diseases,
but not one capable of
changing someone's size.
Giants aren't made.
They're born that way.
Our bodies get bigger and
bigger the longer we stay here.
Why is this happening to us?
No way.
That means their size wasn't caused
by hypersecretion of growth hormone,
but then what could it be?
Need candy! Candy!
They're using these kids
as test subjects. Candy.
Calm down, Allie.
It's going to be OK.
Give it to me!
What is this master guy trying to do?
They're innocent children.
What kind of monster would drug them?
Now the other kids are losing it too!
We can't fight back.
We can hurt them.
No, Sand!
Don't throw it, please!
I'll fight the big guy!
No, you won't!
Get out of my way, Luffy!
Careful!
Don't hurt the children!
Oh, come on! I know!
Special attack sleep star!
Poor kids.
I had a feeling that
they'd been kidnapped.
We need you to help us get out of here!
I want to go home and
see my mommy and daddy!
Luffy, I can't imagine the pain these
children are dealing with right now.
Knowing what they've been
through, it breaks my heart.
They said they want to go home.
They want to see their parents.
We've got to do something.
Yeah, I agree.
We're the only ones who can save them.
Okay, let's put them on the
ship and take them home.
No problem. Come on.
That's never gonna happen.
We can't just waltz out of here, you know.
It's true.
Besides, our theory is speculation.
So we can't be certain of anything
until we meet who's responsible.
Oh yeah, the master.
It's bad timing, though.
Half the crew's looking for that samurai.
Well, it's fine.
I'm sure they'll figure something out.
We can all go to the lab on our own.
Luffy, I'm staying here.
I wish I could go.
I'm so angry about what
he's done to these children.
And I really want to kick his butt.
But I can't leave him.
The kids need me.
I'll protect them.
I should stay too.
We can't leave Chopper here alone.
Whatever! Admit it!
You're scared, huh?
Hey, you guys will be in trouble
if they start rampaging again.
Big time.
All right, that should
keep these giants in check.
I feel kind of bad about this.
Get over it.
These kids are huge.
They can crush you.
Yeah, and we have no idea
when they're going to wake up.
I'm not so sure we should split up.
Think about it.
If we want Trafalgar to switch us back,
we'll have to be together when we see him.
At least I assume that's how it works.
It's a big deal. Stay like this.
That's easy for you to say.
You're still in your own body.
the heart of the leader of
the g5 vice admiral smoker
what a wonderful souvenir
thanks with With this,
the fight is over.
Now that the G5 has lost their warship,
they're bound to attempt to steal
ours in order to make a report.
Of course, I've got men lying in wait.
What about the Straw Hat crew?
No need to worry about them.
I have a plan to get rid of
them and retrieve the children.
Watch.
Those brats will beg to come back.
We won't even have to
lift a finger. You'll see.
Huh?
I didn't think much of the Straw Hats.
That is until Monet warned me about them.
It might be overkill, but I'm
sending those two after their crew.
That's right!
The men known as the
Snow Mountain Assassins!
they never miss their target my
loyal minions the yeti cool brothers
there are six more of them the way
he talked him up I thought they
were gonna be a lot stronger it
should be easy to finish him off
we'll take them down just
like those other three
and we'll do it in a cool way
it's me here's the thing
So far, we've got three. What?
The pirate hunter Zoro.
The cat burglar.
And the soul king.
We left them at the bottom
of a cliff in District F-16.
You'll need to get out there
and recover the bodies.
Hold on.
Did you kill them? Why?
Is that a problem?
Well, I don't know, I mean.
If you didn't want them to end up dead,
then you shouldn't have
asked us to do the job.
It's fine!
The master did say he
wanted them dead or alive!
Now, now.
No need to get so worked up. You're right.
He almost lost it there at home.
Yeah, stay cool. Thanks, gentlemen.
We're counting on you.
Sinororo! Oh, my.
Did you hear?
Three of them are already dead.
I heard.
What a disappointment.
The Straw Hats are part of the worst
generation, as is our friend Law here.
Not only is the government keeping
its eye on them, but so is Blackbeard.
The papers go on and on about them.
I keep reading about how
they're back in action.
I assumed they'd be a lot stronger.
Well, Law?
You know them, don't you?
I understand you've crossed paths twice.
Two years ago at Sabaody, and then
again at the war in Marineford.
Is that true?
Why, you traitor, you didn't
summon them here, did you?
How many times do we have to go over this?
I didn't even know they
were being held captive
in the laboratory until I
ran into them out front.
If I'd known, I'd have told
you to try a different tactic.
Locking them up in an
ordinary cell isn't enough.
let's talk about your negligence i wasn't
able to drive the navy out and it's thanks
to you if this operation were exposed it'd
be just as bad for me as it would for you
master i'm in the middle of an experiment
but it's one of the seven warlords
is it now you want to stay here on punk
hazard it was a pain trying to reach
this place since log posters don't work i
should have known what with this being a
secret government lab and all and why do
you want to stay i assume that since this
used to be dr vegapunk's laboratory there
must be records of all the government
research that's happened here that's as
forthcoming as i'm willing to be right now
here's the deal what i want is free roam
of the lab and the island so what do you
say in exchange I'll provide you with my
assistance and we'll
stay out of each other's
business but there's one condition you
can't tell anyone I'm here not even Joker
so you know do you where'd
you get that information would
you rather an ignorant an
idiot wandering here or someone
like me good point we're birds
of a feather aren't we law
well I don't trust you I see no
harm in your request well Monet
Trafalgar law from the
north blue interesting the
surgeon of death who consumed
an op-op fruit so you're a
doctor are you we've got
several former prisoners who've
been paralyzed by poison gas
you can treat them can't you
it's true I suppose if you'd
called them here you would
have been more discreet you
had to do a lot of sucking
up to the government to
land your cushy warlord job
surely you wouldn't risk
losing it all by making a mess
of things here how silly of
me my apologies listen you
said something about the
children begging to come back
without you even having to
lift a finger what did you
mean by that ah yes they'll
never leave because i've
been giving them drugged
candies it's sweet it's fizzy
and it fills your mouth
with gas ah yes it's also a
stimulant and a highly
addictive one at that if they go
home they won't be able to get
their precious candy anymore
you're one sick puppy aren't
you you remind me of someone
where are you going aren't
you gonna fight the Navy
you can call me if you need
me and I'll bring you the
head of Anyone you want the
clever ones are trouble.
They're hard to manage
Ah!
Not again!
What's going on? Uh-oh.
This isn't an earthquake.
We're under attack!
Ah!
Huh?
What?
Explosions? That's odd.
We just came from that direction.
Do you think it could be tied to
whatever left these footprints behind?
I can sense something, and they're close.
Beast-looking guys. Big ones.
Let's go back.
Nami and Chopper are in danger.
What do I do?
If the cave starts collapsing
on us, they'll be goners.
Luffy, where are you?
We could use your help right now!
There's nobody here but us, so we'll
just have to handle this on our own.
Chopper! You see him?
How many enemies?
Tell me!
Bella!
There's nobody out here!
But how can that be?
I just busted my noggin!
Oh, I fell asleep.
What's with all the ruckus outside?
Maybe someone's come
to rescue me, but who?
Law?
The master? No.
We're in the snowy mountains,
so it's gotta be them. Huh?
I heard that. Spill it.
You know who's attacking, right?
I demand that you tell us,
or else you're gonna pay.
You better not be making fun of lasers!
You're wasting your time
looking for them because
they're never going to
show themselves to you.
We work with them and we don't
know what they look like.
But we do know that once they're paid,
they'll carry out any
assassination without fail.
Everything else is a mystery,
except that their footprints are
huge and their voices are deep.
No, wait.
Also, they're some sort of beastmen, and
they're covered in fur from head to toe,
or so the rumors say.
They prowl the snowy peaks, appearing
whenever a blizzard strikes.
Oh, yeah.
I almost forgot we also know their names.
They're Scotch and Rock.
The Yeti Cool Brothers.
They're from a snowy region,
and they're about 25 years old.
Sounds like you know plenty about them.
But nobody knows what
they look like, Lassie.
Still, they're tough.
And they've come to
this cave to rescue me.
You're in trouble.
If they're here, that means
you're on their hit list! Huh?
You're Brownbeard, aren't you?
Just so you know, you happen
to be on our hit list, too.
Fuck that guy!
He's ginormous and I didn't even
notice him sneak in yet! Huh?
Rock, is that you?
I'm Scotch.
You've come here to kill
me! Wait, no. Sorry.
I must have misheard you.
Man, you really had me scared.
The Master would never have me killed, so
he must have sent you to save me, right?
Well, tell you what, if you untame me,
I'll help you take care of the straw.
You didn't mishear anything.
The Master ordered us to
assassinate you, too. What? No way.
You want proof?
Oh, and while we're at it, what
was that big guy's name again?
His voice.
The one with the silly-looking braided
beard who was captured by the Straw Hats.
You know, the dunce who's
famous for being stupid.
Oh, that's right, Bluebeard! No! Huh?
Is that him?
He's a fool, so it was easy to manipulate
him, but now he's become a nuisance.
I don't need his services
anymore. Kill him!
I was right!
Look, there's smoke!
Nami!
Chopper!
We're on our way!
You're Brownbeard, aren't you?
I'm so glad you've joined us, Brownbeard.
There's no need for you to worry.
I promise that you're safe here.
Anything to report?
No, Master.
It's all clear.
Nothing but snow as
far as the eye can see.
That's good.
Thank you, Brownbeard.
You're a fine patrolman. Huh?
Aw, shucks.
No.
I'm begging you.
Don't do it!
Master!
That'll shut you up.
You shouldn't have lost your cool.
Hey, Scotch! Huh?
That must be the other one!
Don't shoot so recklessly.
This place could collapse and kill
the Brats. Oops. You're right.
That wouldn't be cool.
Brownbeard!
But they're on the same side!
It looks like we've got company.
Their captain's back.
Let's take care of them first.
Oh, crap.
Those guys are scary!
Are they giants? Mama.
Not any kind I've seen.
I'm warning you jerks, you better
not have hurt any of my crew!
What the? Where'd he go?
Help me!
They captured Nami!
Those big jerks took her with them!
The master said he wants this one alive.
Right, the robot would vega punk's lasers!
But we can kill the rest
of them in that case.
Let's take our time and enjoy this hunt!
Sounds cool to me.
It's law.
Where do you think you're going?
You can't leave right now.
Not when the Navy's in the area room.
I don't give a damn.
You guys may not know this,
but I'd go where I want.